Lexus LC car you can get with
installments that are already and high approval rate
through our dealer
our very wide network of all
car dealers makes it easy for you to get
your dream car the existence of
high powered sedan cars and have
sophisticated features has become an
everyday sight in today's era
the ease of applying technology
to the latest four-wheeled vehicles
makes it have
higher and better technology compared to
previous generation cars
the technology used is
changing the face of the car industry as a
whole where one of them is the
Lexus LC 500 car from Lexus a subsidiary of
Toyota which focuses on the
luxury car segment Lexus LC 500 comes
with a very extreme shape and
has very high aerodynamics
armed with only two doors this car is
claimed to have a maximum power that is
quite high reaching
351 to 7100 revolutions per
minute even the Lexus LC 500 is the only
car that uses 10
automatic transmissions to bring out its best performance
sold at a price that is certainly quite
expensive the LC500 certainly has a
variety of comfort and safety features that
make it very respected on the streets
not only that Lexus's ability to
present high powered cars also
deserves a thumbs up engine and dimensions
Lexus LC 500 Lexus LC 500 comes with a
large engine for a
sedan size reaching 5L with a compression ratio of
12 3 to 1 this means
the car can travel 12.3 KM
with just one liter of gasoline for
maximum power lc500 can reach 351 peta
seconds at 7100 revolutions per
minute and maximum power of 540 n m at
4800 revolutions per minute please
note this car has a
fairly high speed from 0-100 km per Hi
Lexus LC 500 can travel in just
40 seconds so it is
very dangerous for ordinary users
considering the dimensions of this car including
having a large size in the
sedan class the overall length reaches 4.7
meters with a car width of 1.9 m and a
height of only 1.3 M has dimensions that are
quite wide it turns out the ground clearance
or distance between the ground and the car is
very low so it is less suitable
for use on roads that are not good
because it can damage the chassis has a
very high speed of course
this latest Lexus car comes with
a variety of the most superior technology
comparable to the money that
prospective buyers have to spend to
get a car that is not produced
in  These mass
technologies can be
seen from how the car's chassis and
suspension work.